<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="demo_text">Demo Text</string>
    <string name="long_text">Before, Miss Tao Zi had been very confused. She didn\'t know what she liked and what she wanted to do? The family\'s requirement for her is to take a primary school teacher after graduation. Many people think that Ms. Tao Zi is good enough to find a job, and she won\'t have much prospects. After meeting Ms. Rabbit, Ms. Tao Zi has a new goal. She wants to become an excellent person and a promising person. Since then, Miss Tao Zi has worked hard every day. Although some people say that hard work is not necessarily useful, you never try to succeed if you never work hard. Later, Ms. Tao Zi was admitted to the graduate school of 985 University with excellent grades, and found a good job after graduation. The current Miss Tao Zi bought a house with the money she earned. The house is not big, but very warm. Ms. Tao Zi rarely talks to others about her changes at the beginning. I know it must be a long and difficult road. Fortunately, she finally lived the life she wanted. I once saw such a story in a book. George Dawson has always been an unknown person until he was 90 years old when he suddenly realized that his life was wasted, and he felt that he should leave something in the world. So he immediately entered the literacy class and began to learn literacy and cultural knowledge. Later, he fell in love with writing and worked tirelessly in this direction. Finally, when he was 102 years old, he completed his debut novel \"The Life of Sogood\". This book caused a huge sensation as soon as it went on the market and became one of the best-selling books in the United States at the time. George Dawson also rose from a little-known little character to a great writer that people love to hear. It can be seen from this story that a person\'s destiny is completely in your own hands. What kind of person you want to be, what kind of life you want to live, whether you want to change or not, and when you change, are all up to you. Therefore, it doesn\'t matter what was yesterday, it is the most important from today.</string>
    <string name="cancel">cancel</string>
    <string name="confirm">confirm</string>
</resources>